(Penny:)Are you gonna make us pretend
to be a bunch of lame characters
(Penny:)with silly accents?
"Lame characters with silly ac...."
What kind of actress are you?
(Penny:)You're right, I'm sorry.
It sounds like fun.
(Raj:)-Thank you.
-That kind of actress. This sucks!
(Leonard:)Come on, guys.
Raj put a lot of effort into this.
(Leonard:)And that's great.
It's not sad, it's great.
(Amy:)I think it might be fun
to be someone else tonight.
(Raj:)Actually, you're all just
gonna be yourselves.
Oh. Ecch!
(Bernadette:)All right, if I'm doing this, I'm
playing to win. So just to be clear,
(Bernadette:)If we're ourselves,
that means one of us killed Stuart?
(Raj:)Very good, Bernadette.
You are a regular Byomkesh Bakshi.
(Bernadette:)What is that, like,
the Indian Sherlock Holmes?
(Raj:)Or is Sherlock Holmes
the English Byomkesh Bakshi?
(Amy:)According to Wikipedia,
Sherlock Holmes came first.
(Raj:)Great, everyone's a Byomkesh Bakshi.